const Quiz = [
  {
    id: 1,
    courseId: 1,
    question: "What is the purpose of sifting dry ingredients in baking?",
    options: [
      "To remove lumps and aerate the ingredients.",
      "To add moisture to the mixture.",
      "To melt the ingredients together.",
      "To increase the volume of the dough.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To remove lumps and aerate the ingredients.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    courseId: 1,
    question:
      "Which of the following is a basic cooking technique that involves cooking food quickly in a small amount of oil over high heat while stirring constantly?",
    options: ["Braising", "Baking", "Grilling", "Sautéing"],
    correctAnswer: "Sautéing",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    courseId: 1,
    question: "What is the primary purpose of kneading dough in bread baking?",
    options: [
      "To add flavor to the dough.",
      "To incorporate air into the dough.",
      "To stretch and develop gluten.",
      "To reduce the baking time.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To stretch and develop gluten.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    courseId: 1,
    question:
      "What is the main ingredient in a classic roux, which is commonly used as a thickening agent in sauces and soups?",
    options: ["Milk", "Sugar", "Flour", "Eggs"],
    correctAnswer: "Flour",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    courseId: 1,
    question:
      "What pastry technique involves folding and rolling dough to create layers of butter and dough, resulting in a flaky texture?",
    options: ["Braising", "Steaming", "Tempering", "Laminating"],
    correctAnswer: "Laminating",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    courseId: 4,
    question: "What does HTML stand for?",
    options: [
      "Hyper Text Markup Language",
      "Highly Technical Markup Language",
      "Home Tool Management Language",
      "Hyperlink and Text Markup Language",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    courseId: 4,
    question:
      "Which programming language is used for adding interactivity and dynamic behavior to websites?",
    options: ["HTML", "CSS", "JavaScript", "Python"],
    correctAnswer: "JavaScript",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    courseId: 4,
    question: "What is the role of CSS in web development?",
    options: [
      "To structure the content of a web page.",
      "To create and manage databases.",
      "To add interactivity to a website.",
      "To style the presentation of a web page.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To style the presentation of a web page.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    courseId: 4,
    question: "What does HTTP stand for?",
    options: [
      "Hypertext Text Transfer Protocol",
      "Hypertext Transfer Protocol",
      "Hyperlink Transfer Text Protocol",
      "High Technical Transfer Protocol",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Hypertext Transfer Protocol",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    courseId: 4,
    question: "What is the purpose of a responsive design in web development?",
    options: [
      "To secure websites from cyber attacks.",
      "To create visually appealing animations.",
      "To ensure the website loads quickly.",
      "To provide an optimal viewing experience across different devices.",
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      "To provide an optimal viewing experience across different devices.",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    courseId: 5,
    question: "What is animation?",
    options: [
      "A style of visual design.",
      "A technique for creating static images.",
      "A process of adding motion to objects.",
      "A way to compress images for the web.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A process of adding motion to objects.",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    courseId: 5,
    question:
      "Which animation technique involves showing a series of still images in rapid succession to create the illusion of motion?",
    options: ["Stop motion", "3D modeling", "Pixel art", "Keyframe animation"],
    correctAnswer: "Stop motion",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    courseId: 5,
    question: "What is a keyframe in animation?",
    options: [
      "The first frame of an animation.",
      "A frame with important content.",
      "A frame that represents a pose or state.",
      "A frame with a special visual effect.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A frame that represents a pose or state.",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    courseId: 5,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'easing' function in animation?",
    options: [
      "To adjust the brightness of the animation.",
      "To add sound effects to the animation.",
      "To control the timing and acceleration of motion.",
      "To change the animation's color palette.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To control the timing and acceleration of motion.",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    courseId: 5,
    question:
      "Which type of animation is best suited for creating realistic character movements in video games?",
    options: [
      "2D animation",
      "Stop motion",
      "3D animation",
      "Traditional animation",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "3D animation",
  },
];

export default Quiz